Jontae Pierce

307 Carrington Green Pkwy, McDonough, GA 30252 205-764-2844

https://github.com/AirForcePier

Linked in profile

jontae.pierce@gmail.com



OBJECTIVE

Exhibit personal experience in the field of web development as a Software Developer of highly maintainable and scalable web applications utilizing the latest client and server-side technologies, including vanilla JavaScript, HTML and CSS, React, Angular, Node, Express, build tools like Gulp, Webpack and Grunt, and transpilation tools like Babel.

COMPUTER SKILLS

Client-side technologies - JavaScript, Angular, React, Backbone, Grunt, Gulp, Babel, Webpack, Bower, HTML, CSS, jQuery

Software packages - Atom, Sublime, Terminal

EXPERIENCE

Electronics Mechanic, Defense Logistics Agency

Robins AFB, GA — March 2010 - September 2015

I performed functional tests, analyzes performance and troubleshoots the electronic, electrical, hydraulic, pneumatic and mechanical functions of the subsystems integrated into the digital brake/antiskid system, maintenance annunciation panel (MAP) system of the integrated main generator, standby generator, emergency generator, flight control power, AC/DC power distribution and sub-systems integrated into the electronic/electrical and environmental systems.

Accomplishments

- Designed and maintained new processes for better time and risk management.
- From fiscal year 2012 to 2015, assisted in 100% on time delivery of C-5 aircraft coming from Programmed Depot Maintenance.
- Developed training program for all new hires and cross training technician to minimize loss time when transitioning into the C-5 Electronics department.

Radar Technician, United States Air Force

Robins AFB, GA — December 2002 - December 2008

Rebuilding, overhauling, installing, troubleshooting, repairing, modifying, calibrating, aligning, and maintaining, integrated systems, i.e., where the output of a number of sensors subsystems are integrated in a logic subsystem and the resultant used to modify the operation of the total system. Examples are: fire control, flight/landing control, bombing-navigation, and electronic warfare or multiple integrated electronic systems composed of several of these systems which are closely interrelated and interdependent.

Accomplishments

- Designed and maintained new training programs for new Airmen
- Performed emergency maintenance overseas for several aircrafts during OEF/OIF
- POC for many vendors and contracted specialists to perform certain maintenance.

EDUCATION

The Iron Yard

Front End Engineering — 2015

University of Phoenix

BS in Information Technology/Software Engineering — 2015 - 2017

Community College of the Air Force

Electronic Principles/Avionics Systems — 2003 - 2005

REFERENCES

Available upon request.